lmctruck.com 2018-12-21

# LMC Truck - Privacy Policy

Effective Date of Current Policy: June 28, 2017

Long Motor Corporation ("LMC") values its customers and respects their privacy. This Privacy Policy covers any of your personal information obtained by LMC, LMC Truck, Victoria British or other entity under which LMC conducts business. The term "LMC" refers to all these entities collectively. If we make any material changes, we will post the new policy here, with a new effective date.

By using LMC's websites which include [www.lmctruck.com](http://www.lmctruck.com/), [www.victoriabritish.com](http://www.victoriabritish.com/) and other names under which we do business (collectively, "Site" or "Websites"), you consent to use of information, including Personal Information, that is collected or submitted as described in this privacy policy.

## What is Personal Information?

"Personal information" is information that can be associated with a specific person and could be used to identify that specific person whether from that data or from that data and other information that LMC has or is likely to have access to. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used to identify a specific person, whether in combination with other information or otherwise.

## What Personal Information Do We Collect?

During a visit to our Site, you may provide us with information that uniquely identifies you including Personal Information such as names, postal and email addresses, telephone numbers or credit card information. We also receive your Personal Information when you access or update your online account or profile, order product, enter a contest or voluntarily submit other information to us.

Our Websites are not directed to children under age 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from them. Children under 13 should not provide their personal information to us through our Websites, to customer service, or in writing.

## What Other Information Do We Collect?

We automatically gather other information when you browse or view our Site. This log data may include your browser type (e.g., Chrome, Safari or Internet Explorer), your domain, the Internet Protocol (IP) address assigned to your computer (or the unique device ID of your mobile device), the date and time of your visits, the pages on our site you visit and other information related to your visit.

## How Long Do We Retain This Information?

We retain your personal information as long as it is necessary and relevant for our operations. In addition, we may retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with national laws, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce our User Agreement and take other actions permitted or required by applicable national laws.

## How Can You Correct Information Retained by Us?

We take steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is accurate and up to date, and that you have the ability to access it and make corrections to it. To make corrections contact us via customer service or at [customercare@longmotor.net](mailto:CustomerCare@LongMotor.net?Subject=Customer%20Contact%20From%20LMC%20Truck%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page) or by mail at the address listed below.

## How Do We Use Personal Information?

We use your Personal Information to transact business with you (purchases, orders, payments, returns/exchanges, requests for information about our products and services, etc.) and to otherwise serve you as a customer.

We may use your Personal Information to communicate with you about our products and services we believe you might find of interest and to administer promotions, surveys, contests and sweepstakes in which you might participate.

We also use your Personal Information to improve the effectiveness of our website, operations, mobile experience, marketing efforts or as described elsewhere in this policy, to prevent against fraud and theft, and otherwise to protect our Site visitors and our business. Our marketing efforts include the use of Google Adwords and Google Analytics, described above.

We may share your Personal Information with our dealers, suppliers and partners, who may provide you with SMS, email and other communications and offers for products and services, including offers based on your interests, personal and business characteristics, stated preferences and location.

Our employees and agents may view your Personal Information to perform their jobs and service your needs. We authorize access to your Personal Information to them on a need-to-know basis to provide you with our products or services to you, or for one of the other reasons listed in this section.

## With Whom Do We Share Your Personal Information?

We may provide your Personal Information to affiliated companies or others who process it on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Statement and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may also release your information, including Personal Information, to others (including law enforcement) if we believe such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or legal process; enforce or apply the terms of applicable terms of use; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of LMC or others.

We may also sell, transfer and disclose your Personal Information as part of a business divestiture, sale, merger, or acquisition of all or a part of our business. If another company acquires our company, business, or assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, Personal Information may also be transferred as a business asset.

We may share aggregate, non-individual information with third parties for lawful purposes.

## How Do We Protect Your Personal Information

We maintain a variety of security measures, including physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. No system can be completely secure, so we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure.

All credit card and electronic payment transactions are processed through a gateway provider(s) and are not stored or processed on our servers. In utilizing this gateway, your payment transaction data and related information may be retained the third parties involved in the banking or credit card transaction. The use of your information by such third party(ies) will be subject to their applicable privacy policy(ies), which you should carefully review. If you purchase items from us and utilize credit card or electronic payment services we share information with third party payment processors to the extent necessary to enable your payment. Credit card payments are processed through Total System Services, Inc. ("TSYS"). Transmission and processing of data by TSYS is subject to their agreement and privacy policy. Details are available at: <http://tsys.com/privacy-policy.html>.

## Other Information:

**Cookies:** We use technologies such as "cookies" and web beacons so we can remember certain information, such as items in your shopping cart or your preferences based on prior or current site activity. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can improve our Site. You may block our cookies or similar identifiers in your browser settings, but if you do, certain features on our Site may not function as well or at all.

**Google Adwords:** We use Google Adwords and Google Analytics to gather data such as age, gender and interests to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain online ads on our Site or other sites because we contract with Google and similar companies to target our ads based on information collected from you or by automated means, like cookies and web beacons. These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

**Advertising Analytics:** You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads' preferences at [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

You may give consent for our Site to capture and record certain precise geo-location or global positioning data from your device in order to tailor information to your location. We may link such location data to other information that you provide to us or that may be accessed in connection with your use of our Site.

You should be able to manage how your mobile device and mobile browser share location information with us, as well as how your mobile browser handles cookies and related technologies, by adjusting your mobile device's privacy and security settings.

There are "do not track" or similar browser choices available to internet users with respect to online web activity, but given the present lack of consensus of what constitutes an informed election, appropriate trigger or breadth of scope of such choice, our Site will not operate any differently when a "do not track" signal is received.

## Social Networking sites

You may be able to post content to on Social Networking Sites (such as Facebook, Instagram, Snapchat or Twitter) on which we maintain a presence. If you choose to do this, we will provide information to the Social Networking Sites in accordance with your elections. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for your use of those websites and that it is your responsibility to review the terms of use and privacy policies. We are not responsible for the availability, accuracy, content, products or services of such Social Network Sites.

## Third Party Links

Our Site may have links or be linked to other sites we do not own, control or maintain. We are not responsible for and make no representations or warranties about the privacy practices of those sites. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of other sites and contact the operator if you have concerns or questions. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these third party sites.

## Legal Matters

We may disclose information you have provided to us if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (1) comply with the law, government action or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property, including without limitation these Websites; or (3) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (by way of example, if you provide false information or pretend to be someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of an investigation).

## Privacy Rights of California Residents

If you are a California resident, you may have the right to request and receive certain information about a company's disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing use, and your choices with respect to such disclosures.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e‐mail to [customercare@longmotor.net](mailto:CustomerCare@LongMotor.net?Subject=Customer%20Contact%20From%20LMC%20Truck%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page), or write us at:  
CA Privacy Rights  
LMC Privacy Administration  
PO Box 14991  
Lenexa, KS 66285  
USA

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any site where this policy is posted, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send an email with a detailed description of the specific content or information to [caprivacy.wdig@twdc.com](mailto:caprivacy.wdig@twdc.com). Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

## International Visitors

Our Site is hosted in the United States. If you access our Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of our Site, you acknowledge and consent to the maintenance and processing of your personal information in the United States and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, you understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing personal information may be less stringent than in your country. You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning our website and/or Services.

## Changes to our Privacy Statement

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time, so please check the "Last Revised" date at the top of this page. Changes will become immediately effective upon posting on our Site unless otherwise noted. Your use of the Site following these changes indicates your consent to the practices described in the revised Privacy Statement. 

## Opting Out of Communication

You may opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email you receive from us or by changing the communication preferences on your online account or profile. If you no longer want to receive promotional text messages from us, please follow the cancellation instructions contained in the last text message. If you are having difficulty unsubscribing from our marketing communications using the above methods, please contact us at [1-800-562-8782](tel:18005628782).

If you opt-out from receiving marketing emails or text messages, we may still need to send you communications about your orders, customer service inquiries, promotions participation and other matters.

If you agreed to receive future marketing communications directly from a third party through our Site, you will need to contact that party to opt-out of such communications. This process may be outlined on that party's Privacy Policy.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or you wish to make changes to your personal information or remove yourself from our database to the extent available, please contact us in one of the following ways: **By Email at:**  
**By Mail at:**  
LMC Privacy Administration  
PO Box 14991  
Lenexa, KS 66285  
USA   
**By Telephone at:**  
[1-800-562-8782](tel:18005628782) • United States  
[1-913-541-0684](tel:19135410684) • WorldWide
